ereaderiq.com 2019-07-01

# Privacy Policy | eReaderIQ

### How Can I Help Support eReaderIQ?

eReaderIQ is a free service which depends on user donations to stay open. You can [visit our 'changes' page](https://www.ereaderiq.com/changes/) if you want to know more.

If you would like to help keep eReaderIQ open, you can [donate via PayPal](http://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&hosted_button_id=3DHUNG4N7N3FY) or [become a patron](https://www.patreon.com/ereaderiq) at Patreon.

Thank you for your support!

_Updated: 2015-01-15_

### Consent

By accessing eReaderIQ ("eReaderIQ", "Website", "we", "our"), you are consenting to our Privacy Policy.

### Information We Collect

eReaderIQ can be used freely and anonymously by anyone. We do however require that you provide some personal information for some of our services including, but not limited to, our daily email newsletter and book alerts. Should you choose to join one of our subscription based services, you may be asked to enter some or all of the following: your name, your email address, your preferred book genres. Should we offer any paid services, payments will be administered through PayPal. Users will be bound by PayPal's Privacy Policy and Terms of Service.

### How We Use Information We Collect

Any of the information we collect from you is used to improve your experience on eReaderIQ. It is used to personalize your browsing experience, improve our Website and to administer contests, promotions and giveaways.

We do not divulge any of our collected information to third-parties. Any and all the information collected by eReaderIQ will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, disclosed or loaned. Any information you provide will be held with the utmost care and will not be used in ways that you have not consented to.

### Cookies

For purposes of our Website, a cookie is defined as a small file stored on a user's computer that collects and stores information about the user. In addition to Cookies, we may use a session ID cookie which is an information file that collects data that terminates when the browser is closed. We also may use persistent cookies that remain stored on a user's hard drive for an extended period of time. We utilize Cookies for user convenience and to save personal preference choices that you set during visits to the Website. We do not use Cookies to track personal information such as an email address or phone number. You may disable any cookies already stored on your computer, but doing so may stop our website from functioning properly.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to our website. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visit to our site and/or other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

### Third Party Links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our Website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Affiliate Disclosure

Some of the links posted on eReaderIQ are "affiliate links." This means if you click on a link and purchase an item, we may receive an affiliate commission. Clicking on these links does not affect the price you pay for an item.

### Privacy Policy Modifications

eReaderIQ may revise our Privacy Policy at any time without notice. By using our Website you are consenting to the current version of our Privacy Policy.

### Terms of Service

Visit our Terms of Service page to view the terms and limitations governing our Website. [Click here to view our terms](https://www.ereaderiq.com/terms/).
